<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>Yoru&#x27;s Asoulless Space</title>
      <link>https://asoulless.space</link>
      <description>Yoru&#x27;s website</description>
      <generator>Zola</generator>
      <language>en</language>
      <atom:link href="https://asoulless.space/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
      <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
      <item>
          <title>Anthropic banned my account, and that&#x27;s a good thing</title>
          <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
          <author>Yoru C. Jiyuu</author>
          <link>https://asoulless.space/blog/anthropic-ban/</link>
          <guid>https://asoulless.space/blog/anthropic-ban/</guid>
          <description xml:base="https://asoulless.space/blog/anthropic-ban/">&lt;p&gt;I had an Anthropic account a bit ago. I originally got it because I wanted to try to find a use for generative AI for myself, and based on a look at &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.anthropic.com&#x2F;legal&#x2F;privacy&quot; class=&quot;external&quot;&gt;their privacy policy&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; and how they train their models, I decided on Anthropic’s Claude. This time had been the second that I had made an Anthropic account, as the phone number requirement for making an account annoyed me so much that I just deleted my account the first time. I eventually made a new one later when I was trying to learn how to use it for programming (that was at least my reason then). At the time, my dad was using ChatGPT but eventually switched away from it for Claude, which he’s using now (he’s told people before that I got him onto it, but I honestly don’t remember even mentioning it to him 😅). In fact, he liked it so much that he not only got a Pro plan, he got me one, too.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A bit after Dad paid for a Pro plan for me, though, I tried to log into the app on my phone one day, only for the app to tell me that my account had been suspended or banned. It was incredibly confusing at first, but I eventually started to put the pieces together. When he had first paid for the plan, I got a receipt for that plan. Exactly 10 days later, I got another receipt (multiple, actually) about a refund of that payment. I didn’t know why I got it at first, but once I realized that they refunded my dad when they banned my account, it made more sense. Still confused as to why my account was banned, I sent them an appeal, trying to explain some of the possible reasons why they could have banned me.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It wasn’t until 2 weeks after, which was Monday, December 29th, a few minutes before midnight, that I got a rather generic response back from them telling me that they weren’t going to reinstate my account. I couldn’t even reply to the email to try and get some more information as to exactly what I had done wrong that had violated &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.anthropic.com&#x2F;legal&#x2F;aup&quot; class=&quot;external&quot;&gt;their Usage Policy&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;, as they said that I had done.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The best that I could hypothesize on why they banned my account may lie in the account details. See, when I made my account, I didn’t use my legal name. I did this to protect my privacy when I shared chats with people, as I didn’t want my real name out on the internet. I made this decision before my dad paid for a Pro Plan, so once he had done so, I didn’t think to change it to my actual name. So, when their systems looked at my account and saw something (by their definition) fishy going on, they looked into it, and saw an account with an oddly fictitious name using the credit card of a real person. So they made the decision to pull the plug on the account and refund the credit card holder their “stolen” money. But of course, this is only a very far-fetched guess at best. There could be another reason, but I have yet to hear anything from Anthropic about this. Either way, I’d take my hypothesis with a grain of salt.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I thought about it some more, though, I realized that it could’ve been a blessing in disguise.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My time with Claude – and even other generative AI services like Proton’s Lumo and even ChatGPT – hasn’t been groundbreaking. I used Claude for a few things, including,&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Troubleshooting server setup issues when I was trying to set up my home servers again.&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Trying to get an API up and running when I had an idea to make a REST API so I could learn the technology (I didn’t develop it any further, but you can view it &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;github.com&#x2F;asoulless&#x2F;flavor-text&quot; class=&quot;external&quot;&gt;here&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;).&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Trying to write up descriptions for jobs and experiences that I had on LinkedIn. I didn’t use what Claude gave me verbatim, but tried to use it as a starting point for what I eventually used. I even informed it of this, though I don’t remember it really changing the output of it that much, if at all.&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There were a few other things that I used it for, but they all fall under the same idea that I’ll talk about later.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My dad, on the other hand, uses generative AI a lot, even before using Claude. He would use it to put together documents, research things, brainstorm ideas, and probably more things that I can’t think of. But he doesn’t seem to use it blindly: he’ll correct it when it gets stuff wrong. He doesn’t use it for everything, but he makes good use out of it. Far better use of it than I could, whether I wanted to or not.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thinking back on my time with Claude, I only ever used it when I was mentally moving at Mach 34,085 in a 30 mph zone, and I wanted an answer &lt;em&gt;now&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;. It was useful when I wanted to do something, but I didn’t want to slow down to try and learn how to do it. Take the REST API I mentioned earlier, for example. I had an idea, I wanted to get it out fast before I lost interest in it, so I turned to Claude for help in trying to get it up and running. My brain was already moving at light speed, and I wanted to keep going, not slow down and possibly lose interest. It’s about as effective as vapes for a cigarette smoker: it &lt;em&gt;may&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; be healthier, since you’re not dealing with the tobacco and carcinogens, but you’re ultimately just giving someone else money for a difference of possible issues.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So with that being said, I think it’s a good thing that Anthropic banned my account, no matter what I had actually done to violate their Usage Policy. Why? For one, my dad gets to save money on another subscription that likely would’ve gone underutilized in my opinion, leading me to try to force more uses of it into my life. But more importantly, I won’t be able to use a &lt;em&gt;good&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; AI model (good on the basis of it being better than others). Something that I’ve been thinking about lately is the effects of generative AI. Not only on the environment, but also on me as a person. I haven’t really seen my light usage of Claude have much of an effect on me, but that isn’t to say that it &lt;em&gt;hasn’t&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; had an effect on me. However, knowing now how much I tend to get locked in, mentally moving a million miles per hour, I can see now that generative AI only helped me maintain that habit of going too fast instead of taking the time to slow down and think about things. So, losing access to that was like losing a high-quality vape, though unlike a vape, I may not be able to get a “good” AI model again. I may struggle with having to get myself to slow down at times, but at least I’ll be getting the practice in.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So thank you, Anthropic, for banning me from using the (if not some of the) most ethical AI models out there. I hope that others find your services more useful than I could.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;details&gt;
&lt;summary&gt;Post-writing notes&lt;&#x2F;summary&gt;
&lt;p&gt;oh my goodness i actually sat and wrote an entire blog post in an single sitting without any music or anything. what the heck.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;okay, the original draft i did in a single evening, the editing and the banner art didn’t, though lol. i don’t think so, at least.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;actually, scratch that, i did it all in the same day-ish. thank You Jesus. let’s freaking goooooooooooooooo&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;details&gt;</description>
      </item>
      <item>
          <title>Why I decided to start an actual blog</title>
          <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
          <author>Yoru C. Jiyuu</author>
          <link>https://asoulless.space/blog/whyblog/</link>
          <guid>https://asoulless.space/blog/whyblog/</guid>
          <description xml:base="https://asoulless.space/blog/whyblog/">&lt;details&gt;
&lt;summary&gt;Music I was listening to while writing this&lt;&#x2F;summary&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was mainly listening to 2 Mello’s &lt;em&gt;Sunsound Collisions&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; album at 80% speed. While you don’t have to listen to it at that speed while you read this short post (or listen to it at all), if you want to set it to that exact speed, you can set the speed in the video settings by selecting the cog in the bottom right of the video, and setting the video speed to &lt;code&gt;0.8&lt;&#x2F;code&gt;.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;details&gt; &lt;summary&gt;Click this to see an image of where this is in the YouTube embed&lt;&#x2F;summary&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;&quot;alt=&quot;The settings menu as seen in the YouTube embed with 4 options: Stable Volume, Subtitles&amp;#x2F;CC, Playback speed, and Quality. Playback speed has a red outline around it, and is set to 0.8&quot;src=&quot;yt speed.png&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;details&gt;
&lt;iframe
	class=&quot;youtube-embed&quot;
	src=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.youtube-nocookie.com&#x2F;embed&#x2F;Ua0_JA4xQQg&quot;
	allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&quot;
	referrerpolicy=&quot;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;iframe&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;details&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I remade my website, one of the biggest reasons for this was so that I could start a proper blog in the same place as my personal space on the internet. It was a wish mainly inspired by many of the websites that I had seen on the indie web (and especially &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;daudix.one&quot;&gt;Daudix’s website&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;) that followed the same practice. As I had stated on the page for &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;asoulless.space&#x2F;projects&#x2F;patch-notes&#x2F;&quot;&gt;The Patch Notes&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;, I had already been doing that in some capacity on that public Logseq graph.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My original decision to publish some pages of my Logseq graph came from my own reason to use Logseq in the first place. Originally, I was doing my journaling in a Word document. But as time went on, I found myself having a harder time focusing on just writing, as I would get mentally stuck while trying to think of something to write about from that day. I then decided to try to use Markdown files to jot down thoughts to write about later, later found out about and tried using Logseq, and eventually, &lt;em&gt;that&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; ended up being the app that I was using to journal with. Logseq made it so easy for me to link together ideas and write in a format that matched my disjointed thought process that I just continued to use it. Once I realized that I could publish pages of my graph publicly, I realized that I could get my messy thoughts out there! &lt;em&gt;I could say something!&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But alas, I’m trying something new here: I’m starting a proper blog. Not one made of disjointed blocks of text, but one made of properly formatted paragraphs and such. Why? For a few short reasons:&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First, because &lt;strong&gt;the way that I see it, writing is nothing more than methodically combining and organizing a bunch of ideas to express them.&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt; It’s a way of expressing oneself. It’s really cool to me, and it’s something that I want to try out for myself. Besides, I’m going to have to do it in the future if I’m going to somehow get the elusive 20-figure job that my parents seem to want me to get. But that’s a minor reason for wanting to write more. It’s important, but I’m not focusing on it for that reason. Of course, it may not be that special to some people, but for me, whose brain seems to be constantly moving, it’s very fascinating.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This actually leads me into my second reason: &lt;strong&gt;starting this blog and actually making posts for it actually forces me to slow down.&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt; I was recently introduced to another way to look at the current issues that I have in contrast to my current one: it may not be that I’m just struggling to connect ideas together, but that I’m just going too fast (that’s at least how I understood it). Thinking about it, it actually started to make sense. My brain seems to be running on a constant rhythm that never seems to slow down; I don’t like slowing down at all, so whenever someone or something interrupts me, it actually feels like someone came at me with an entire freight train.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So yeah, that’s about it: I’ve seen people make their thoughts look pretty, so I wanna make my thoughts look pretty, too. &lt;del&gt;i sound like a little kid saying that lol&lt;&#x2F;del&gt; Hopefully, I continue to keep this updated and write stuff for this blog.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</description>
      </item>
      <item>
          <title>Change</title>
          <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
          <author>Yoru C. Jiyuu</author>
          <link>https://asoulless.space/blog/change/</link>
          <guid>https://asoulless.space/blog/change/</guid>
          <description xml:base="https://asoulless.space/blog/change/">&lt;details&gt;
&lt;summary&gt;Music I was listening to while writing this&lt;&#x2F;summary&gt;
&lt;del&gt;stealing something else from Mambuco&lt;&#x2F;del&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the second day of writing this, I started listening to Madeon’s &lt;em&gt;Good Faith&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; album. I didn’t listen to the whole album while I was writing it, as that would’ve been too distracting for me, but I did listen to his acoustic set on loop:
&lt;iframe
	class=&quot;youtube-embed&quot;
	src=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.youtube-nocookie.com&#x2F;embed&#x2F;U1aB0Ylb_00&quot;
	allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&quot;
	referrerpolicy=&quot;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;iframe&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;details&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As of late, life has felt… boring, for lack of a better word.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s not necessarily that I’m bored; I have plenty of things to do, but… life doesn’t feel like it has anything worth working for.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My parents have been telling me to get a job for years, even while I was still in &lt;del&gt;High School EX&lt;&#x2F;del&gt; college. While I only feel marginally closer to that goal now, I, unfortunately, still don’t really have much of a personal desire to get a job. No amount of money or the things that it could get me could drive me to actively try to get a job that doesn’t even seem to exist in today’s job market. I trust that they just want me to be well-off in this country, but it still doesn’t drive me to earnestly try, even if I try to for their sake.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recently, &lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;android-developers.googleblog.com&#x2F;2025&#x2F;08&#x2F;elevating-android-security.html&quot;&gt;Google has announced plans to basically lock down Android in the name of security&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; by making it so that you can only install apps made by developers that Google verifies. It was thanks to this that, for once, I seriously considered switching to iOS. Why? Because those changes would have basically turned Android into that same operating system, but under a company that likely cares less for your privacy. Even now that &lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;android-developers.googleblog.com&#x2F;2025&#x2F;11&#x2F;android-developer-verification-early.html&quot;&gt;they’ve announced that they’ll have an “advanced flow that allows experienced users to accept the risks of installing software that isn’t verified”&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;, an iPhone as my next phone is still looking appealing. It doesn’t feel worth trying to be personally invested in a device whose designers clearly don’t want you to make it your own.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And for bonus points, hearing and seeing political news, especially in the U.S., only exacerbates this feeling even more. I don’t even look for political news; the Invidious instance that I frequent has the popular feed set as the home page (though that’s more on me; I could always change it on my end and set a cookie), and my sister will often times bring political news that she sees in her own feeds to me (nothing against her by any means; I’m sure she’s just trying to vent her frustration).&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All of these things have had me feeling pretty down as of late, save for when I’m playing &lt;em&gt;Persona 5 Royal&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; or working on some other personal projects of mine. It’s getting to the point where I’ve actually started wondering if I’m struggling with depression again. Especially before I started writing this last night, as I was feeling down again, but I was having a hard time tracing it back to anything. However, I think I have more of a theory as to why I’ve been feeling so down as of late, as well as what may have been hindering me all these years.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;relationships&quot;&gt;Relationships&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I often go down what I call “mental rabbit holes” in my mind, which are typically scenarios that I walk through despite me reminding myself that they &lt;del&gt;very, very likely&lt;&#x2F;del&gt; won’t happen. As much as I hate to admit it, they repeatedly revolve around romance. Not viewed through rose-tinted glasses, but, ironically enough, through the lightning and flashes of &lt;em&gt;fear&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;, of all things. As creepy as it may sound, relationships are quite fascinating to watch from afar. I’ve come to understand them as two people deciding that they’re going to stick together through this hell of a rollercoaster that we make light of by just calling it “life”. Put another way, they’re life partners. It’s this and the small moments of affection that they show one another that never fail to make me smile. So, if that’s the way I see them, then how could I experience fear during these types of mental rabbit holes?&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Notice how I referred to people in these relationships as &lt;em&gt;life&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; partners. Not “partners for this project”, not “partners for a time”, &lt;strong&gt;life&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt; partners. It means that they stay together for the rest of their lives. The problem with this, though, is that, as living beings, we all have this special ability that, though others can attempt to snuff it out, can never be killed: it is the ability to choose, the ability to make choices; it is &lt;a class=&quot;colored&quot;&gt;｢free will｣&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;. With this ability, we can choose to stay in these life partnerships, and we can choose to love our partners. However, with this ability, we can also choose to act in ways that harm our partners, harm those who depend on us, or we can ultimately decide that we don’t want to continue in this relationship anymore. That is, &lt;strong&gt;we can choose to change&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-singular-constant&quot;&gt;A singular constant&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;They (whoever “they” is) say that the only constant in this world is change. The only thing that will ever stay the same is that things will change.&lt;&#x2F;small&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For most of my childhood, my parents have been divorced. Eventually, my siblings and I were doing the whole split custody shenanigans, spending some time with our mom and some time with our dad for at least 8 years of my life. Split custody solves the issue of making sure that both parents who can’t peaceably live together can still spend time with their kids, but it solves this problem at the cost of &lt;em&gt;stability&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;. The children will never really be able to truly settle down as they move back and forth between places. Even if it’s between two places that always stay the same, the environment never remains stable (this is based on my own experiences; I haven’t done my research, but every child is different, and the effects may also be different).&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, the constant back and forth, combined with other factors in one parent’s house over the other, led me to learn, on a very low level, that &lt;em&gt;everything can, and often will, change&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;. As contradictory as this may sound, that doesn’t produce an adult ready to take on a constantly changing world; it produces a child still holding on to what little stability they have left. This doesn’t even take into consideration the undiagnosed autism I was dealing with.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;fear-of-the-singular-constant&quot;&gt;Fear of the singular constant&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My own internal fear of change is something that has crossed my mind before, but it is only now that I’ve come to realize just how much it has affected me.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With Google seeking to change who can make apps that people can use, even if it’s in the name of “security”, the biggest reason for me to stay on Android was under the threat of changing. So, my solution was to simply move to a system that would mainly be the same with better privacy and just stop investing myself into the device.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hearing about political news both here in the U.S. and in various other countries causes me to feel like things are constantly changing. Constantly seeing change happen, I find myself fearing that the world is on the verge of a major change that will rock the entire world to its core. Every single piece of political news causes just a small change that often doesn’t impact me directly, but it does make me fear what could be next.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A job doesn’t interest me because, in my mind, I have to somehow manage to appeal to the employer’s desires for an employee in order to get the job. On top of that, even if I manage to climb that ever-rising peak, then I’m left at the mercy of my employer for my well-being. I think the recent tech industry layoffs with the advent of generative AI are proof enough of this fact. Of course, I could attempt to make sure that I’m always employed by staying up to date with the newest technologies, but I don’t want to deal with a rat race that continues to grow at hyper-exponential speeds. Even if I were to get hired at some company making lots of money like my parents want me to, I would likely live in fear that I could simply not make the cut when they start laying people off. In other words, I would constantly fear that things would simply change, and I wouldn’t be able to change fast enough to keep up.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A relationship, while fascinating and beautiful to me, doesn’t interest me because of my constant fear that she could change. I would fear that she could suddenly become disinterested in me, or possibly worse, that she starts to choose to stay with me out of obligation rather than because she enjoys staying with me. What may be even worse is that the same thing could happen to me, too. I could change to her detriment, making me feel horrible and guilty for something that I would constantly fight, possibly in vain, to rectify. Either way, I would constantly fear that she could change and either choose to leave or stay with me in a prison of her own making, or that I could change and do either of the same things…&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A bit of a tangent, but my dad has repeatedly given me some advice concerning looking for a wife, based on the advice that a pastor gave in a book on the subject: that you go on up to 3 dates with her, and it’s by the third one that you decide whether you’ll date her (or something like that). I’ve always hated this piece of advice. At first, I understood my disdain for it to come from the fact that it felt like just too little time to decide on something like that. You’d think that whoever gave the advice was going for a speedrunning record (nothing against the pastor, by the way). But now, I have a different understanding of the issue: 3 dates feels like too little time because it’s not enough time for me to strengthen my faith in her so that I can come to believe that she won’t change and that she actually wants to be with me. If I should go through 4 seasons before getting married to her, then scratch that; I need somewhere around &lt;em&gt;40&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A significant other leaving, being laid off from a job, a major change in the world, or Google wanting to change Android. In my stability-craving mind, the possibility of one of those things happening makes me fear that my fragile understanding of reality itself will be upended. An event as catastrophic as the earth itself suddenly exploding, leaving me suspended in space attempting to live in a space that’s not my own (that is, if I survive the explosion). I don’t want to invest time and energy into something that I’ve learned will simply fall apart at some point in the future, so I just… don’t really work towards anything at all. At best, I explore ideas, I float around the web, and I watch the world change from my mental faux shelter. All while everyone attempts to convince me to come out and play a game where the meta changes once a millisecond.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;so-what-do-i-do&quot;&gt;So… what do I do?&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To be honest, I’m not really sure. All of this is just a theory as to why I haven’t felt motivated to do all of these things that everyone around me seems so eager to do.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course, I could “just deal with it”, but that only seems effective in a &lt;em&gt;Saw&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; movie where you’re basically guaranteed to get cut, injured, or killed. A better solution may just be to just have more faith in people that they won’t change on me, though that seems pretty vague.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Either way, I’m not really sure what I could really do, but I at least feel closer to the source of the problem.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</description>
      </item>
      <item>
          <title>Heart of the Heartless</title>
          <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
          <author>Yoru C. Jiyuu</author>
          <link>https://asoulless.space/heart/</link>
          <guid>https://asoulless.space/heart/</guid>
          <description xml:base="https://asoulless.space/heart/">&lt;p&gt;Souls, and the Ones who reach out to them,&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These are the ones that make up reality.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The tales of their experiences, the bonds that they share,&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And the freedom to choose how their story will go.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</description>
      </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
